question_data=[{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the game &quot;Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code&quot;, you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"The protagonist in &quot;Humanity Has Declined&quot; has no discernable name and is simply referred to as &#039;I&#039; for most of the series.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"General Knowledge","question":"NCIS stands for &quot;Navy Corps Investigative Service&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Vehicles","question":"In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"Druid is a mage class in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Mythology","question":"Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Number 16 Bus Shelter&quot; was a child&#039;s name that was approved by the New Zealand government.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"All of these maps were in &quot;Tom Clancy&#039;s Rainbow Six Siege&quot; on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"Throughout the entirety of &quot;Dragon Ball Z&quot;, Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Geography","question":"Switzerland has four national languages, English being one of them.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Comics","question":"In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Computers","question":"The T-Mobile Sidekick smartphone is a re-branded version of the Danger Hiptop.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Computers","question":"DHCP stands for Dynamic Host Configuration Port.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Politics","question":"Joko Widodo has appeared in the cover of a TIME magazine.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"TF2: Sentry rocket damage falloff is calculated based on the distance between the sentry and the enemy, not the engineer and the enemy","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Celebrities","question":"Lady Gaga&#039;s real name is Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"History","question":"The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3\/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"In the &quot;Kagerou Daze&quot; series, Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"History","question":"Joseph Stalin&#039;s real name was Ioseb Bessarionis dze Dzugashvili.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]